Mankind's Deadliest Threat Will Not Come From The Skies.
Night Shadows is a horror, science fiction, thriller
film directed by John "Bud" Cardos.
When two brothers, Josh and Mike, go to a small southern town for a
vacation, they find most of the residents either dead or missing.
When Mike himself goes missing, Josh teams up with the local sheriff and an attractive school teacher to find him until Josh discovers that the whole town and most of
it's people have been infected by a form of toxic waste, and they have all turned into toxic vampires whom prowl the streets at night for human blood!
Josh Cameron, played by Wings Hauser.
Sheriff Will Stewart, played by Bo Hopkins.
Holly Pierce, played by Jody Medford.
Mike Cameron, played by Lee Montgomery.
Albert Hogue, played by Marc Clement.
Billy, played by Cary Guffey.
Mutant is a 1984 American horror film.
It was initially released to theaters as Night Shadows, but it premiered on video with
the Mutant title, which it has retained for all subsequent releases.
The film explores themes of sheriff, motel, toxic, zombie.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.